<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lesson on Ode: An Ode to Lost Knowledge.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/lesson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lesson on Ode: An Ode to Lost Knowledge.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/lesson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Fallacy of Relegion in Pakistan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/fallacy-of-relegion-in-pakistan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/fallacy-of-relegion-in-pakistan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fallacy of Relegion in Pakistan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan holds a distinctive place in history as the only nation that achieved independence primarily on religious grounds. Established on August 15, 1947, it was founded on the principles of Islam. However, from its inception, the country has grappled with defining its true identity, with religion playing a complex and often ambiguous role in its development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the time of independence, the ideological and philosophical direction of Pakistan was uncertain. Muhammad Ali Jinnah, the nation’s founder, had lived most of his life as a non-practicing Muslim. While he advocated for the establishment of a Muslim-majority state, his vision for Pakistan did not align with religious extremism. In his notable address on August 11, Jinnah articulated a secular vision for the country, emphasizing that citizens of all faiths should enjoy equal rights and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Legend of Khan Shaheed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/the-legend-of-khan-shaheed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/the-legend-of-khan-shaheed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“The very ink with which history is written is merely fluid prejudice&amp;quot;. It is infuriating and dispiriting at the same time that this man is not celebrated enough in Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A free thinker, a phastun revolutionary, a freedom fighter, a feminist, the independence icon and the anti-imperialist hero, and the man who spent 33 years in jail – Abdus Samad Achakzai, the Gandhi of Baluchistan.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Pakistan, it often feels like the entire freedom struggle was fought by just two people: Quaid-e-Azam Muhammad Ali Jinnah and Allama Iqbal. It’s almost as if the nation believes that the entire fight for independence was won by a handful of men, and the rest were just there to hold the flags and cheer from the sidelines. But if we look a little deeper, we find that many other leaders, like Abdus Samad Achakzai, played crucial roles in shaping Pakistan’s history—though, of course, no one remembers them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Myth of Sisyphus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/the-myth-of-sisyphus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/the-myth-of-sisyphus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Myth of Sisyphus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sisyphus, the cunning king of ancient Greece, is remembered for his trickery and rebellion against the gods. Born in Corinth, he ruled with wisdom and cunning, often surpassing those around him. One of his most famous feats was to outwit Thanatos, the god of death, and prevent people from dying. This act of rebellion angered the gods, who decided to punish him in the most impossible way possible: Sisyphus was condemned to roll a huge boulder up a hill forever. Each time he got close to the top, the boulder rolled back, forcing him to start over, forever, with this pointless task.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
